>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好吧，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, well,
我们回来讨论这一问题的解决方法
we're back to talk about the solution
to this this-heavy exercise.
希望你的手指没有穿过这个点
Hopefully your fingers are not too
worn out from typing this dot and
把所有地方都绑好
.bind all over the place.
所以正如我所说的我们想做的就是想重新定位
So as the read me indicated,
what we wanna do is we wanna reorient from
定义了使我们的对象成为对象的工作坊函数，并定义我们自己的对象。
the define workshop function making our
object, and define our own objects.
所以在某种程度上
So in a way,
我们只需要在这里复制所有这些功能
we really just need to copy all of
these functions that exist down here.
我们需要复制所有这些内容，并将它们放入对象文字中。
We need to copy all of them, and
put them into an object literal.
所以我就开始做这个
So I'll just start doing that.
我说 deepJS = 一个对象文字。
I'll say deepJS = an object literal.
然后我就直接把我所有的功能都放在这里
And then I'll just put all of
my functions directly in here.
除此之外，我将把所有这些
And in addition to that,
I'm going to turn all of these
在简洁的方法中因为我不想做财产分配
into the concise method form, because
I don't wanna do property assignments.
给我点时间我把这些都放上去
So give me just a moment
while I wire all these up.
这里有很多功能，不是吗 ?
There's a lot of functions here,
aren't there?
>> Kyle Simpson: 好的，我们在他们之间需要逗号，所以
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, so we're gonna
need commas in between all of them, so
别忘了
don't forget that.
>> Kyle Simpson: 这是有关类语法的一个很好的部分，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That is one nice
part about the class syntax,
不需要到处使用逗号。
is not having to deal with
the commas everywhere.
我会给他们这个决定是个好决定
I will give them that,
that was a good decision.
好吧我们去履行职责吧
All right, so let's take out function.
我要用一个替代的方式来做
And I'm just gonna do that with a replace.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Put that one back.
>> Kyle Simpson: [COUGH] 好，现在我们需要将属性 currentEnrollment
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: [COUGH] Okay, now we need
to put the properties currentEnrollment
和 studentRecords 我们得把这些都放在上面
and studentRecords,
we need to put those on there.
因此，我们将有 currentEnrollment， >> Kyle Simpson: 是空数组。
So we'll have currentEnrollment,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Is an empty array.
studentRecords 为空数组。
And studentRecords is an empty array.
现在我们要把所有这些点都扔在任何地方
And now we need to start throwing
in all our this dots everywhere.
所以我们引用了一个我们引用的财产
So anyplace that we reference a property
that we were referencing lexically as
一个变量，或者当我们引用一个现在是一种方法的函数时，
a variable, or when we reference
a function that's now a method,
在它前面需要点这个点
it needs a this dot in front of it.
所以我要把这几个圆点写在这里，反复写。
So I'm just gonna write a lot of this
dots over and over and over again.
this.currentEnrollment。
this.currentEnrollment.
this.printRecords ，带有 this.currentEnrollment 。
And then this.printRecords,
with this.currentEnrollment.
和 this.currentEnrollment 。
And this.currentEnrollment.
还有 this.paidStudents 。
And this.paidStudents.
还有 this.print
And this.print.
还有这个提示
And this.remind.
和 this.currentEnrollment 。
And this.currentEnrollment.
还有 this.studentRecords。
And this.studentRecords.
matchId 是此处的实际功能，不需要此点。
matchId is an actual function in here,
it doesn't need a this dot.
this.getsStudentFromId。
this.getsStudentFromId.
然后这个点，不，不记录，但是
And then this dot, nope, not records, but
this.sortByNameAsc 和 this.printRecord。
this.sortByNameAsc and this.printRecord.
没有一个需要这个点，没有一个。
And none of those needed this dot,
none of those.
此点，此点和 this.getStudentId。
And this dot, and this dot,
and this.getStudentId.
和 this.currentEnrollment 。
And this.currentEnrollment.
有人厌倦了在所有东西面前打字和看到这个点吗 ?
Anybody tired of typing and
seeing this dot in front of everything?
这是一种非常详细的编码方式。
This is a very verbose style of coding.
[ COUGH] 我们需要 this.notYetPaid。
[COUGH] We need this.notYetPaid.
和 this.printRecords。
And this.printRecords.
和 this.getStudentFromId 。
And this.getStudentFromId.
现在我们需要关注有方法引用的任何地方
Now we need to take care of any places
where we have method references that need
要强硬的人
to be hardbound.
让我们回去吧
So let's go back through and
查找作为回调传入的任何方法。
find any methods that are getting
passed in as callbacks.
这不是一个财产的方法，这样就可以了。
That's not a method that's a property,
so that's fine.
那就好那就好
That's fine, that's fine, that one's fine.
没问题的
That one's okay.
在这里， this.getStudentFromId ，这是一种方法。
Here we go, this.getStudentFromId,
that's a method.
所以它会失去它的束缚，所以我们需要一个点来约束它。
So it's gonna lose its this binding,
so we need a dot bind this.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 然后在这里，用 sortByName 排序
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then same thing here,
sorting with the sortByName and
然后用 printRecord 打印。
then printing with printRecord.
那些需要束缚的人
Those need to be bound.
再接着一个，需要装订。
And then another one,
needToEnroll needs to be bound.
getStudentId 需要绑定，
And getStudentId needs to be bound,
> > Kyle Simpson: notYetPaid 需要
and,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: notYetPaid needs to be
绑定。
bound.
应该是这样的
And that should be it.
好吧我们去处理那个工厂的功能
Okay, so
let's get rid of that factory function,
我们现在已经做得很好了
cuz we're very much done with that now.
>> Kyle Simpson: 现在，我们具有此 deepJS 对象，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now that
we have this deepJS object,
这些电话应该是一样的
these calls should basically be the same.
因此，如果我们要运行这个代码，我们还是应该得到同样的打印输出。
So if we were to run this code, we should
still end up getting the same printout.
所以这只是一个实施的改变，而不是外部的变化。
So this was just an implementation change,
not an outside change.
所以让我们试着， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
So let's just try,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Running
在我们的 RunJS 环境中。
over here in our RunJS environment.
>> Kyle Simpson: Uhh，我犯了一个错误，我在哪里打电话?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Uh-oh,
I made a mistake, where did I call?
是啊我忘了别这样叫 defineWorkshop
Yeah, I forgot,
can't call defineWorkshop like that, oops.
所以让我回去吧
So let me go back.
>> Kyle Simpson: 请将其取出，并在其中放置分号。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Have to take that out and
put a semicolon there.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在让我们看看这是否有用。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now
let's see if that works.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 还有我们的打印输出。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And there we go,
there's our printout.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，我们重构这一感知的问题
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So questions on
our refactoring to that this aware
编码样式，此名称空间模式?
style of coding, this namespace pattern?
>> 扬声器 2: 我猜测对象设计类型，对象创建模式，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I guess given the kind of
object design, object create pattern,
你会以务实的态度
would you pragmatically
expect to have namespaced
在你的实践中使用这种多种方法的对象吗 ?
objects with this many
methods in your own practice?
还是你想把它进一步分解 ?
Or would you try to break it down further?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，我的意思是，一般来说，如果我要创建一个对象，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, I mean, generally
speaking, if I'm gonna create an object,
就像个像个 namespaced 一样的东西我唯一能做的就是
like a namespaced kind of a thing,
the only reason I'm gonna go that approach
而不是模块式的原因是我知道我有两个或三个对象
instead of going the module approach is
because I know I have two or three objects
我想通过一个原型链把它们联系起来让他们彼此合作
that I want to link through a prototype
chain and have them work with each other.
所以我要试着把这些东西分开
So I'm gonna try to have those objects
have their properly separated out
而不是把一个巨大的东西和厨房的水池
behaviors rather than having one
giant thing with the kitchen sink of
所有东西都在其中
everything in it.
我要用这三个单独的物体
I'm gonna try these three separate
objects that each do their own thing and
它们几乎是通过调用上下文组成的。
they virtually compose
through that call context.
好吧我希望这方面的编码能有点启迪
Okay, well, that hopefully was a bit
enlightening on the this-aware coding,
还有一些你可以遇到的问题
and some of the problems
that you can run into.
它们不仅仅是异步回调和事件处理程序，
They're not just with asynchronous
callbacks and event handlers,
即使你把你的那些冷酷无情的东西都变成了
even those callbacks that you
pass into things like array.map,
你得担心这个束缚
you have to worry about the this binding.
所以你得小心点
So you need to be careful.
我想说的是我在这里所做的捆绑使用的总量
I would say on the whole the amount of
bind usage that I had to do here was
在我之前说过的边界线上，这种编码方式是不有用的。
on the borderline to where I would have
said, this style of coding is not useful.
把这个点放在所有东西面前是非常详细的。
It certainly was very verbose to put
this dot in front of everything.
而且我很可能支持
And I probably would have
favored the module pattern for
这种特殊的代码是吗
this particular kind of code, yes?
>> 演讲者 3: 对此有约束力的规则是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: What's the rule for
binding this?
有时它是用它有时也不是
Cuz sometimes it's using it and
sometimes it isn't.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，这的确是个好问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah,
that's actually a good question.
这里有几处地方
So there's a couple of places.
我很高兴你把这个给我了有几个地方
I'm glad you brought that up,
there's a couple of places I should have
回去说我们真的需要吗
gone back and said,
do we actually need it?
例如， sortByName，
So for example, the sortByName,
我们不需要它因为它没有在它前面提到这个点
we don't need it because it doesn't make
a reference to a this dot in front of it.
所以这实际上是不必要的，和 printRecord的相同。
So here, that was actually unnecessary,
and the same thing with printRecord.
这是不必要的，因为我们没有这方面的任何参考资料。
It was unnecessary there because we
don't have any this references in it.
所以说的话，你的问题的答案是，
So in order words,
the answer to your question is,
仅当方法是此感知功能时才需要绑定此功能。
you only need to bind this if
the method is a this-aware function.
我们在这里有一些功能在命名空间上
We have a few functions on here
that are on the namespace but
不知道，所以不需要装订。
are not this-aware, and so
they don't need a binding.